daveramsey.com 2018-06-28

# DaveRamsey.com

## Our Policy Behind Our Privacy Policy

The Lampo Group (“we” or “us”) refuses to make you read through pages and pages of boring text about a policy that does nothing but trick you into not reading it. Because we have every intention of protecting your privacy, we have made our privacy policy clear and concise enough that you will read it and feel comfortable using our site. We're here to help you, not put you to sleep!

This Privacy Policy discloses our privacy practices and how we may use the information that we gather on our website, www.daveramsey.com (the “Site”) or that you provide to us through other means. By using the Site or voluntarily providing personal information to us, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site and sets forth the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared;
  2. What choices are available to you regarding our use of your data;
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information; and
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Respecting the privacy and the security of your personal information is important to us. We realize that providing us with personal information is an act of trust. Therefore, we have created a Privacy Policy to show you the steps we have taken to secure that trust. Please take a few moments to read this policy carefully.

## Collected Information

Each time you visit the Site, we may automatically collect certain types of information. Some examples of automatic information we may collect are as follows:

  * We may record your internet service provider's address, your internet protocol or IP address, the web page from which you came, your web browser software, the type of handheld or mobile device used to link to the web page, and the language settings on your web browser;
  * We may collect a record of your activity or your “clickstream” while visiting the Sites;
  * We may use “cookies” of different types to recognize your computer. A cookie is a small text file that a website, online application, or e-mail may save to your internet browser and/or your computer's hard drive for use in subsequent visits to the Sites or other sites. For more information, see our Cookie Policy below;
  * We may use web beacons, match scripts, pixel tags or similar technologies that allow us to know if a particular web page was visited, an e-mail opened, links in the email utilized or if the advertisements on the Sites or other sites were effective. In some instances, these technologies may allow us to match activities with particular users; and
  * We may also collect any information you enter, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or debit card information.

## Use of Information

We will use your information to fulfill orders you have placed, to better understand and serve your needs, and respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We may also use your personal information to enhance your customer experience, improve our customer service, tailor offerings and advertisements to you relating to services you have requested, and communicate with you about products, services, special offerings offered by The Lampo Group that may be of interest to you.

We may also use this information to analyze and manage our businesses. Aggregate or combined data is collected from online and offline facilities and may be used to enhance the ability of The Lampo Group to communicate with you and to support business functions such as internal business processes, marketing, authentication, customer service, fraud prevention, and public safety and legal functions.

Your information will not be accessible to anyone other than our staff or business affiliates whose services you have requested. All that to say, we won't sell your information to all the spammers that clutter your inbox!

We make every effort to keep you informed of our own special events, news and offers. Periodically, we send announcements via email or direct mail. If you do not wish to be contacted by our office, simply click on the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email newsletter. If you have susbscribed to multiple email newsletters from The Lampo Group, you can unsubscribe from each newsletter individually or use the unsubscribe page to remove yourself from all future marketing emails.

_Note: We'll have to hand over the information you provide if we're ordered to do so by a court of law._

## Sharing of Information

We may share your personal information with third parties, including third-party service providers. Some examples of the services that third-party service providers offer include:

  * Authorization of debit card and check transactions, order fulfillment, service promotions;
  * Developing, hosting or maintaining the Site on behalf of The Lampo Group;
  * Aggregating customer information and/or improving customer service. We may then share such aggregated information with prospective marketing partners and advertisers.

These service providers are granted access to some or all of your personal information as necessary and may use cookies (as defined above and below) or other automatic collection technology on our behalf. The service providers are contractually restricted in the ways they may use your personal information.

Moreover, in the event that a division or part or all of The Lampo Group is bought, sold or otherwise transferred, or is in the process of a potential transaction, customer information will likely be shared for evaluation purposes and included among the transferred business assets.

The Lampo Group may also disclose specific information when such disclosure appears necessary to comply with the law, a subpoena or other litigation process or to protect the interests or safety of its visitors and customers, employees or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any;
  * Change/correct any data we have about you; or
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.

## Do Not Track

Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) has not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals and therefore, The Lampo Group and the Site do not recognize DNT.

## Cookies Policy

The Site uses "cookies," which are small pieces of information stored by your browser or other application on your computer's browser or hard drive. The cookies are used to connect your computer with information stored about your online activity, searches, preferences and product purchases both within the same website visit and from one visit to the next on the Site and/or other websites. Some examples of this data include your account preferences, user specific information on pages accessed, searched terms or addresses entered, and previous visits to the site. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive new cookies or how to disable cookies altogether. If you reject cookies, you may not be able to participate in certain activities or receive a promotion tailored to you. The Site does not control and does not guarantee the effectiveness of browser-based tools for managing cookies.

We or our partners may also use Flash cookies (also known as Local Stored Objects) or other similar technologies. A Flash cookie is a small data file placed on a computer using Adobe Flash or similar technology that may be built into your computer or downloaded or installed by you to your computer. We use these technologies to personalize and enhance your online experience, facilitate processes, and personalize and store your settings. Flash cookies may help our website visitors to, for example, set volume preference associated with a video experience, play games and perform surveys. They help us improve our Sites by measuring which areas are of greatest interest to customers. They may be recognized by other sites or by our marketing or business partners. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies and the cookie management tools provided by your browser may not remove Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies or other similar technologies, please be aware that you may not have access to certain features and services that make your online experience more efficient and enjoyable.

## Security

We are determined to keep your information private. We use industry-standard security techniques on the Site to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from you at the Site. We have even added measures to protect your personal information during transactions. For example, when you supply us with your debit card or checking account information to make a purchase, we encrypt your information to ensure a safe and secure transaction. Your payment information is temporarily stored on a secure server before processing. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us. In this regard, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data while you are on the Internet. At a minimum, we encourage you to make sure that you are using a secure browser as you surf the Internet.

### How to Correct, Access, and Update Your Information

If you wish to access information that you have submitted through this Site or to request the correction of any inaccurate information you have submitted through this Site, please call **888.22.PEACE**.

## Updates or Changes to the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time as we add new features and services, as laws change, and as industry privacy and security best practices evolve. When we do so, we will post the new Policy on this page and change the date at the bottom of the Policy. We encourage you to return to this page to check for any updates or changes. If we make any change to this Privacy Policy regarding use or disclosure of Personal Information, we will provide advance notice on the Site. Small changes or changes that do not significantly affect individual privacy interest may be made at any time and without prior notice.

## Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites, including those of our business partners. While we seek to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other sites.

## Children’s Privacy

### Under Age 13

The Lampo Group does not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information online without parental consent, we will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from our databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by law). If you become aware of any personally identifiable information we have collected from children under 13, please contact us at [info.general@daveramsey.com](mailto:info.general@daveramsey.com) or by calling **888.22.PEACE**.

### Under Age 18

Minors under 18 years of age may have the Personal Information that they provide to The Lampo Group through the Site deleted by sending an email to [info.general@daveramsey.com](mailto:info.general@daveramsey.com) requesting deletion. Please note that, while we make reasonable efforts to comply with such requests, deletion of your personal information does not ensure complete and comprehensive removal of that data from all systems.

## Contact

Please contact us if you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy. You are welcome to call our Customer Care Center at  **888.22.PEACE**  between 8:30 a.m. and 5:30 p.m. CST to speak with a customer service representative. You may also contact us by e-mail at [privacy@daveramsey.com](mailto:privacy@daveramsey.com).

### The Lampo Group

1749 Mallory Lane  
Brentwood, TN 37027 

Effective Date: May 12, 2017
